### Contact

65, Moshalashi Street, Iponri, Surulere, Lagos. 07052053780 (Work) zubairidrisaweda@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ zubairidrisaweda (LinkedIn) zubs.github.io (Personal)

### Top Skills

**PHP** 

Node.js

Laravel

## Languages

English (Full Professional)

#### Certifications

Introduction To Python And Machine Learning

**PHP Tutorial** 

# Idris Aweda Zubair

Software Engineer at HumongouS.io Lagos

## Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), PHP, HTML, JavaScript, and Web Development. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelors focused in Computer Engineering from University of Lagos.

# Experience

DSC Unilag Member October 2019 - Present (1 year 10 months)

HumongouS.io Software Engineer March 2021 - June 2021 (4 months)

CitonHub Junior Backend Engineer November 2020 - January 2021 (3 months) Nigeria

CodeTouch Technologies Web Developer December 2019 - November 2020 (1 year)

## Education

University of Lagos
Bachelors, Computer Engineering (2020 - 2024)